Elizabeth Herrejon

Engineer, Designer, Builder.

Objective

Award-winning, multi-lingual electrical engineer with 1+ years of experience in research and development for defense and military companies. Strength focuses on troubleshooting, designing circuits, and applying fundamental electrical principles learned in class to the research completed at work. Addition experience generating technical diagrams and building cable assemblies with expertise in developing Labview GUI, VISIO, and hardware maintenance.

Education

Electrical Engineering Major & Robotics Minor, Georgia Tech, Atlanta,

1-2020 onward

GA GPA: 3.23

Math Major, Georgia State University, Atlanta, GA

7-2018 to 12-2019

GPA: 3.66

STEM Engineering Program, Walton High School, Marietta, GA

7-2014 to 5-2018

GPA: 3.8

Skills

NI Labview: Able to create user interfaces, code hardware components, design station setups using DAQs

Microsoft Office: Proficient in Excel, Word, Powerpoint, Visio, Publisher, Visual Studio, etc.

Editing Software: Sony Vegas Pro, Adobe Platforms (Photoshop, After Effects, Audition, Premiere, etc.), Logic Pro, AutoDesk software

(Revit, AutoCad, Inventor), Google SketchUp, Final Cut Pro, Google Colab, Jupyter Notebooks, Solidworks

Languages/Scripts: Experience in C++, Java, Arduino, Labview, Python

Operating Systems: Windows (v.7 and up), iOS (Mac v.10 and up), Linux (Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7)

Other: Great communication and presentation skills, work well under pressure, team player, write grant summaries

Activities

SHPE Scholarship Recipient	5-2020, 5-2021
HSF Scholar Recipient	12-2020
Recipient of OMED Gold Academic Transfer Award	9-2020
GSU Hackathon: Honorary Mention (Cryptology)	10-2018, 3-2019
Founder of MESS: Universal Dysgraphia Pen (STEM Capstone Project)	6-2017 to Present
Georgia Tech Music Technology Earsketch Competition	12-2017
Purdue STEP Summer Program	7-2017
Georgia Tech Music Technology Summer Program	6-2017
Co-Founder & Vice President, Society of Women Engineers NEXT	8-2016 to 5-2018
Participant Inventure Challenge at Walton, Georgia Tech	2015-2016

Work Experience

Electrical Engineering Research Assistant Spring 2020 - ATAS

1-2020 to Present

Worked with the System Design Division to support various engineers in SSD to troubleshoot circuits, create circuit diagrams, build cable assemblies, and generate technical diagrams. Received Interim Security Clearance and worked on various projects assisting engineers by checking, building, and creating systems to practice and expand on fundamental electrical principles learned in class.

GTRI Undergraduate Research Internship Program - Robotic Behavior Development (URIP)

5-2021 to 7-2021

Worked with the creation and composition of robotic primitive skills to create flexible behaviors on a 6 degree-of-freedom robotic system in order to create dexterous grasping and manipulation behaviors with a robotic arm with integrated force/torque and vision sensing. Coded in python to develop a deep learning program, Mask RCNN, to catalog and identify different types of electrical connectors using a custom dataset with noise to run training and inference on unmarked images and videos.

Admin Support Student Assistant - Support Services Department (SSD)

5-2019 to 12-2019

Worked under the guidance of an administrative manager to perform different business administrative duties such as creating manuals and spreadsheets, organizing and distributing keys to new employees at 762-B11, create name tags, assign keys in TMA, look over different architectural drawings to assign positions for moving employees, and manage project schedules and office coordination.

GT CODA-Portman Project, Atlanta

6-2017

Worked on site at the headquarters of the CODA project where construction plans were reviewed and modified daily to incorporate the needs of engineers. Some of the duties performed included calculating the volume for the basement support columns and organized project files.

Integral Construction Inc., Atlanta

6-2017 to 7-2017

Reviewed plumbing, electrical, landscape, and mechanical architectural drawings for different engineers while directly editing the files to upload to the company shared drive. Used both AutoCad and Revit to complete the edits.